Guide to the Ann Greyson Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Ann Greyson Papers,
1971-2000
Greyson, Ann, 1969-
1 linear ft. (ca. 600 items in 2 boxes).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library. New York, NY 10027.
4077413
Biographical Note
Producer, writer, and stage manager. She was born in New Jersey and raised in Atlanta GA and New York City. Her credits include stage manager of The Odyssey Theatre production of "Bremen Freedom" in Los Angeles and the Hofstra University production of "Guys and Dolls".
Scope and Content
Correspondence, contracts, reviews, brochures, fliers, and photographs of various theatrical productions involving Ann Greyson.
Permission to publish materials must be obtained in writing from the Librarian for Rare Books and Manuscripts.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 2 series:
Scrapbook #1
Scrapbook #2
Subjects
Hofstra University.; Odyssey Theatre Ensemble.; Theater--United States.; Women in the theater.; Broadsides.; Brochures.; Contracts.; Photographs.; Reviews.; Actresses.; Authors, American.; Stage managers.; Theatrical producers and directors.; Woman authors, American.; Woman theatrical producers and directors.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located on-site.
Acquisition
08/14/2000 M-00-08-14 Papers Greyson, Ann Gift
Gift of Ann Greyson, 2000.
- Scrapbook #1
  - City of Summit. Summit Health Department Birth Certificate of Ann Greyson, 18 January 2000, (1 page(photocopy)) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Greyson, Ann Correspondence, [v.p.], 1993 & 1995, ( 2 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Glendale Community College FA-99 Final Grades for Ann Greyson (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hofstra University Identity Card for Ann Greyson, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Ann Greyson, [v.p.], 1972-1995, (14 photographs) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - UCLA Extension Award Notification to Ann Greyson, CA, 1997, (3 notofications) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Angels in America, 1992, (1 clipping ) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Berlin To Broadway, 2000, (8 programs and advertisments) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bremen Freedom, 1997, (13 programs, advertisments, and reviews) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Candy & Shelly Go To The Desert, 1990, (8 programs, advertisments, and photographs) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Come Back To The 5 & Dime, Jimmy Dean, Jimmy Dean, 1990, (9 programs, advertisments, audience list, and photographs) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Greyson, Ann Essays and Exams, CA, 1995-1999, (11 essays and exams) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A Girl's Guide To Chaos, NYC, 1992, (13 agreements, programs, advertisments, and photographs) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Guys and Dolls, NYC, 1992, (10 programs, advertisments, and reviews) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - I Want Somebody New, NYC, 1992, (3 advertisments, and VHS jacket) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian Affairs, NYC, 2000, (7 advertisments, programs, and review) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln Center Calendar of Events, NYC, 1990, (3 calendars) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and advertisments, [v.p.], 1992-2000, (15 items) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pandora, NYC, 1990, (9 programs, advertisments, photographs, and letter) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peggy, NYC, 1990, (2 programs, 1 photograph) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pizza Girls, NYC, 1999, (5 programs, advertisements, and review) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Scrapbook #2
  - The Blue Bird, Los Angeles, 1997 & 1998, (27 reviews, photographs, agreements, schedules, lists, correspondence, and advertisements) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bluebeard, Loa Angeles, 1995, (28 advertisements, correspondence, reviews, agreements, lists, and receipts) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bluebeard, Loa Angeles, 1995, (21 programs, advertisements, and photographs) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Hollywood United Methodist Church Floorpland and pamphlet, CA, [n.d.], (1 floorplan, 1 pamphlet) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and advertisements, New York & Loa Angeles, 1995-1999, (17 clippings, tearsheets, and advertisements) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Ring and the Book, Hollywood, CA, 1998 & 1999, (25 reviews, photographs, advertisements, receipts, correspondence, and programs) (Box 2, Folder 27)